Guide to the Vause W. Marshall Papers, 1768-1940
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Vause W. Marshall papers 1768-1940
Marshall, Vause W.
494 Items
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Vause Marshall Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library in 1955.
Biographical Note
Resident of Williamsport house in Burlington (Mineral Co.), W.V.
Collection Overview
Collection consists of correspondence, legal documents, bills, receipts, Civil War muster rolls, clippings and business printed matter, and a diary.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Marshall, Vause W.
United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865 -- Registers
Muster rolls
Clippings
Diary
Photographs
Contents of Collection
- Accession 48-2376
  - Contents of Box 1: (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, 1901-1940
    - Legal Papers, 1790-1927 (2 folders)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1803-1873
    - Photographs
  - Contents of Box 2: (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, 1799-1900
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence
    - Diaries and Sermons ( 3 volumes)
    - Clippings and Printed Materials, 1856-1931
    - Muster Rolls, 1866-1874
    - Miscellaneous Papers, 1866-1874